【翻译制作】微博@电灯泡diandp    *专注新片  内含度盘分享*
舒服 不不不
♪ Suave, no, no, no, sí ♪
哎哟赞
Oh, fuck yeah.
门怎么关着 麦克斯
Why's your door closed, Maxie?
爸 我六年级了 也需要隐私
Dad, I'm in sixth grade. I need, uh, privacy sometimes.
我要去机场
Oh. Look, I'm heading to the airport.
两天后回来
Be back in two days.
对你妹妹和善点
Please be nice to your sister,
多帮帮老妈 别碰无人机
help your mom, and do not touch the drone.
我不会的 拜 -我说真的 好吗
I won't. Bye. - I-I'm serious, okay?
无人机不是玩具 是我工作用的 -好
It's not a toy. It's for my work. - Yep.
一路顺风 拜 爸 爱你
Safe flight. Bye, Dad. Love you.
谢谢
Thank you. Hey.
来给我抱抱
Come give me a hug, bud.
你回来后 我给你两个抱抱
I'll give you two hugs when you get back.
我明白了
I get it.
你笑什么 -你长大咯
Why are you smiling? - Well, you're just growing up.
我很兴奋 -没有 别猥琐地笑
It's exciting to me. - It's not. Stop smiling.
记得我把你从医院接回家
I remember bringing you home from the hospital
恍如昨天
like it was yesterday.
而你现在 在自我慰安
Now here you are, sexually masturbating yourself.
不 我没有 -没事的 傻瓜
No, I "F"-ing wasn't. - Hey, it's cool, fool.
就像你有了新玩具 世上最好玩的玩具
It's like you got a new toy... the best toy in the world...
你只想玩新玩具
and you just want to keep playing with it.
我不知道
I don't know.
我想跟你说 我为你骄傲
I just want you to know I'm proud of you.
好 你忙你的 过几天见
Okay, do your thing. I'll see you later.
爱你 两天后见
Love you. See you in two days.
艾米 你不会相信的
Amy, you are not gonna believe this.
兄弟们 看啊
Yo, guys, check this out.
我保姆告诉我 六年级的人都有手活
My babysitter told me everyone in sixth grade gets hand jobs.
什么是手活
What's a hand job?
就是女孩帮你撸 直到你"哭"
It's when a girl jerks you off until you "coom."
然后你收拾干净就行
And then it's your job to clean it up.
我不觉得这很"酷" -嗯
I don't think it's "coom." - Yeah.
小弟弟会"哭"
C-U-M. "Coom."
中学里呢 比小学更激烈
Middle school's way more intense than elementary.
我们要共度难关
If we're gonna get through this,
我们要团结 -永远的精豆小子
we need to stick together. - Bean Bag Boys for life.
减速带
Speed bump.
你约大学男生 你朋友嫉妒吗
Are your friends jelly you're dating a college guy?
有几个嫉妒的
Some of them, I think.
是吗 -是啊
Yeah? - Yeah.
等等
Wait, hey, c...
需要帮忙吗 -撤退 撤退
Can I help you? - Retreat! Retreat!
怪奇物语们 去死
Hey, Stranger Things, go fuck yourself!
快 -走走走
Hurry! - Go, go, go!
你认识那几个死小子吗
You know those fucking guys?
没人能挡得住"乌兹卡的图赞"卡牌
No one can stop the Turzan of Uzkara.
卢卡斯 把牌放回盒子
Lucas, keep it in the case.
这张牌值300美元
Dude, it's worth 300 bucks.
现价600 我查过了
600 now. I checked.
600美元 -我们是百万富翁啊
$600?! - We're millionaires!
嗯 -明天放学后 去滑板公园吗
Yeah. - Do you guys want to maybe go to the skate park tomorrow after school?
我知道什么是可卡因
I know what cocaine is.
安娜贝尔 出去
Annabelle, get out of here.
此处仅限精豆小子
Bean Bag Boys only.
我听说在滑板公园
I heard, at the skate park,
大小子会让你吸毒
the older kids will make you take drugs.
我们绝不吸毒
We'll never do drugs.
毒品有害生命和社区
They destroy lives and communities.
你别无选择
You have no choice.
妈
Mom!
安娜贝尔 别和你哥较劲
Annabelle, don't antagonize your brother.
来 现在上楼去
Come on, go upstairs. Now... Hey.
好 精豆小子 结束 明天还要上学
All right, Bean Bag Boys, finish up. It's a school night.
8:30熄灯
Lights out, 8:30.
什么啊 你说过8:45的
What? You said 8:45.
收拾干净
Hey. Finish up.
我不想去滑板公园
I don't think I want to go to the skate park.
我们现在六年级了
We're in sixth grade now.
就该做六年级的事
We need to start doing sixth grade things.
你想见柏丽 是不是
Ooh, you want to see Brixlee, don't you?
嗨 -天哪
Hi. - Oh, my God!
妈
Mom!
这公园真燃
This park is fucking lit.
兄弟们 看 滑板车小分队
Yo, guys, the Scooter Squad is here.
知道谁擅长嘲人吗 是阿提库斯
You know who's really good at burns? Atticus L.
他超搞笑 -阿提库斯?
He's so funny. - Atticus L.?
我会在嘲人大战中呛死他 对吧 麦克斯
I'd smoke him in a burn war. Right, Max?
那你给柏丽做的项链 打算送她吗
So, are you gonna give Brixlee the necklace you made her?
没有 闭嘴
No, shut up. It's-it's...
我还没放进窑里呢
I haven't put it in the kiln yet.
你总找借口
You always have an excuse.
索尔 你没和女生说过话
Thor, you never talk to girls.
泡妞容易分心
Girls are a distraction.
两天后有摇滚年代试演
Rock of Ages auditions are in two days.
我不想被束缚
♪ And I don't want to be tied down. ♪
麦克斯 过来
Max, come here.
嗨 泰勒
Hey, Taylor.
据说你在美术课上为柏丽做了项链
People are saying you made Brixlee a necklace in art class.
真会试探 但在成品之前我拒绝透露
Nice try, but I don't talk about my art projects before they're finished.
如果她迷你
If she had a crush on you,
你会承认迷她吗
would you admit you had a crush on her?
她迷我吗
Does she have a crush on me?
我不知道 我从没问过她
I don't know. I've never asked her.
明天见 -拜
See you tomorrow. - Bye.
操
Fuck.
战况如何 小爱神
So, how'd it go, lover boy?
她可能知道项链了
Uh, she might know about the necklace.
晚餐吃蔬菜千层面
Veggie lasagna for dinner?
好事成双 卢卡斯
Everything's coming up Lucas.
学校见
I'll see you guys at school.
拜 注意安全
Bye. Be safe.
滑板车小子来了 冷静一点
Yo, Scooter Boys. Scooter Boys. Act cool.
一定要冷静 -好
Act... act cool. - Okay, okay, okay.
你好哇 阿提库斯
What's up, Atticus?
想见识见识厉害嘛
You guys want to see something cool?
那当然
Hell yeah.
要干嘛 去干什么
What are we up to? What are we doing?
来啜啤酒
We're gonna sip a beer.
怕了吗 -没有
Scared? - No.
我啜过5000口啤酒
I've had, like, 5,000 sips of beer.
得了吧
Bitch, please.
索伦的记录是三口
Soren has the record. Three sips.
三口么 -三口
Three sips? - Three sips.
有点上头
I'm already feeling something.
美味
Delicious.
小心 很带劲
Careful. It's hot.
你喝还是不喝
Are you gonna drink it or not?
我忘了
I forgot,
我这星期五有音乐试演
I have musical auditions this Friday.
他们对啤酒药检
They drug-test for beer.
索尔 承认你是个孬种
Thor, just admit you're a scared little-wittle baby.
不 我不是
No, I'm not.
要不要把啤酒放在奶嘴杯里 奶嘴娃?
Want us to put the beer in a sippy cup for you, Sippy Cup?
不 -奶嘴娃
No. - Sippy Cup.
真嘲 阿提库斯 -一点都不嘲
Amazing burn, Atticus. - It's not a good burn.
他爸两次酒驾 只能搭火车上班
His dad has two DUIs and has to take the train to work.
这才嘲
That's a good burn.
奶嘴娃 给我们唱首歌
Sippy Cup, sing us a song.
不
No.
来首"一闪一闪小精精"如何
How about "Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Bitch"?
奶嘴娃 奶嘴娃
Sippy Cup! Sippy Cup!
不 不 兄弟们
No, no, guys.
他会唱的 但他要多考虑下
He'll do it, but he just needs more time to think.
奶嘴娃 奶嘴娃
Sippy Cup! Sippy Cup!
拜
Bye.
千层面 配苏打水
Lasagna and soda?
你给我吃这个 别告诉我爹妈
Don't tell my parents you gave me this.
这孩子很逗
This kid is hilarious.
我们要离婚
We're getting a divorce.
你们什么意思
Wh-What do you mean?
好 其实一切都不变
Okay, okay, I'll tell you. Everything gonna stay the same.
我们保证
We promise.
还会全家共看《我们这一天》吗
Will we still watch This Is Us together?
当然会 -是
Yes, of course. - Yes.
那是我们最爱的剧
That's our favorite show.
那是我们的家庭剧
That's our family show.
区别就是你现在得用两台电视看
Except now you're gonna see it on two-two different TVs, you know.
在两个不同的家里
In two different houses.
所以你一集得看两遍
So you're gonna have to watch the episode twice.
星期二卷饼日怎么办
What about Taco Tuesday?
卷饼日仍照旧
Taco Tuesdays are still going down.
其实你每周两次卷饼日
Matter of fact, you're gonna have two Taco Tuesdays,
星期三多一次
just one on Wednesday now.
乐趣翻倍
Twice the fun.
乐趣翻倍 卷饼翻倍
Twice the fun, twice the tacos.
所以一切照旧
It's... everything's gonna stay the same, so...
一切照旧 我和你妈妈
Everything gonna be the same. Me and your mom, you know,
我们还是最好的朋友
we're still best friends, right?
全家共吃卷饼很好 但我有个建议
I mean, it would've been nice to have tacos together as a family, but how about this?
卷饼日改成星期三
We could change it to Wing Wednesday...
索尔 灵感 天使之声
Thor, inspired, voice of an angel, man.
感觉不好吗
♪ And don't it feel good. ♪
感觉确实不错
It does feel good, don't it?
怎么了
What's wrong?
那首歌总让我难过
That song always makes me sad.
别忘了 摇滚年代试演是明天
Don't forget, Rock of Ages auditions are tomorrow.
这是我最喜欢的音乐剧
It's my favorite musical.
我现在改变很大 自从
I did make some pretty big changes, though,
我在好莱污走红以来
based on my time in Holly-weird.
我的事迹 一定能鼓舞有梦的人
I think it'll really inspire those of you who dare to dream.
变态
Sick.
于是我看着她 但她看向另一侧
So, I looked at her, but she was looking the other direction.
但后来她看我
But then she looked at me,
我却换了一个方向
and I was looking the other direction.
所以总有一天 我们会对上眼
So I think that someday we're gonna make eye contact.
酷
That's cool.
这部音乐剧要火
This musical is gonna be lit.
索伦
Hey, Soren.
你看他
Look at this.
奶嘴娃报名参演音乐剧喔
Sippy Cup is signing up for the musical.
苦逼劳动力才唱歌
Singing is for try-hards.
不是啦 有人替我报名 是开玩笑
No, uh, someone signed me up as a joke.
我正划掉我的名字 看
I was just crossing it off. See?
随便怎样 逊咖
Yeah, whatever, bitch tits.
够了 我们走
Enough. Let's go.
我还有事 -对不起 索伦
I have places to be. - Sorry, Soren.
别听阿提库斯的
Don't listen to Atticus.
他爸都不交税
His dad doesn't even pay taxes.
阿提库斯说什么 并不重要
Doesn't matter what Atticus says.
我小时候就不想唱了
I've been thinking about quitting singing ever since I was young.
快 鱼糕要被吃完了
Come on. We're gonna miss fish sticks.
我见过的最佳午餐
Whoa. That's the best lunch I've ever seen.
对 我父母超级好 因为
Yeah, my parents are being super nice because...
因为
because...
他们很棒
they're great and...
他们很棒 一切都好
they're great, and ev-everything's good.
等等 那是新耳环吗
Ooh, wait. Is that a new earring?
是的 终于啊 感谢关注
Yes, finally. Thank you for noticing.
你戴耳环很可爱 -麦克斯 我不需要可爱
It looks cute on you. - Max, I'm not going for cute.
我需要性感和热辣
I'm going for sexy and hot.
这是我唯二的选择
Those are the only two things I'm looking for.
你喜欢吗
You like it?
好像被感染了
It looks infected.
索伦真酷
Soren's so cool.
我听说他揍了德里克·巴赫曼
I heard he beat up Derek Bachman
还吹箫他妹妹
and blow-jobbed his sister.
他吹自己亲妹妹?
He blow-jobbed his own sister?
不 他吹的是德里克的妹妹
No, he blow-jobbed Derek's sister.
传奇啊
Fucking legend.
索伦在喊我
I think Soren's calling me.
奶? -奶?(奶嘴娃)
'Sup? - 'Sup?
听说你喝啤酒很猛
I heard you sipped a beer like a fucking champ.
对 我喝了一大口
Yeah, I took a pretty big sip, actually.
酷
Cool.
我明晚办趴
I'm having a party tomorrow night.
这些傻子都来
All these fools are coming.
你来吗
You in?
你该来
You should come.
信我
Trust me.
我会来的
Yeah, I'll come,
但你知道 我得问我妈
but, you know, I'll have to ask my mom.
号外 这是亲嘴趴
Also, gonna be a kissing party.
你有舌吻经验吧
You've French-kissed girls before, right?
有
Yeah.
当然
Of course.
在哪
Where?
嘴?
Their mouths?
答对了 亲
Yeah, dawg.
他不会去和万人迷坐吧
He's not gonna start sitting with the popular kids, is he?
不 如果有人坐那边 该是我
No. If anyone should be over there, it's me.
听说你被叫奶嘴娃
We heard kids were calling you Sippy Cup,
之所以告诉你
and we just wanted to let you know
是因为反霸凌联盟随时欢迎你
you can always call on the Student Coalition Against Bullying for protection.
这像奶嘴杯吗
Does this look like a sippy cup?
非也 这是果汁盒
No, it's a fucking juice box.
因为我不是小屁孩
'Cause I'm not a fucking child.
别无礼
That's so rude.
等下 索尔和卢卡斯能玩趴吗
Wait. Can I bring Thor and Lucas?
太不着调
So random.
不 他们很酷
No, they're cool.
我要男女均衡
I'm trying to keep it half girls, half guys.
懂我吗
You feel me, dawg?
我懂 但
I feel you, dawg, but...
他们是我最佳老友
they're my best friends.
我们什么都一起 我们是精豆小子
We do everything together. We're the Bean Bag Boys.
这名字酷毙了
That's a dope-ass name.
那带他们来
Fuck it. Bring 'em.
我也哈我的小伙伴
I ride or die for my squad, too.
告诉我你妈的决定 亲
Let me know what your mom says, dawg.
好 拜 亲 拜 亲们
Okay. Bye, dawg. Bye, dawgs.
如何
So?
索伦刚邀请明天我们参趴
Soren just invited us to his party tomorrow.
索伦 -是啊
Soren? - Yeah.
他有提起我名字"索尔"吗
He said my name? He said "Thor"?
差不多 -赞
Pretty much, yeah. - Sweet.
那里会有女生 懂意思吗
Oh, there's also gonna be girls there. You know what that means?
逢场作戏
Drama.
亲嘴
Kissing.
你们懂亲嘴吗
So, do you guys know how to kiss?
完全不懂 -不懂
I have no fucking clue. - No.
一点不懂
No, not at all.
键入"亲嘴"
Type "kissing."
不不不 键入"胸部"
Ooh. No, no, no. "Boobs."
"乳腺癌研究"
"Breast cancer research."
"如何匹配合适胸罩"
"How to find a bra that fits."
我有个主意
I have an idea.
"年满18岁?"
"Are you 18 or older?"
我要点击"是"
I'm gonna click "yes."
我们未满18岁
We're not 18 or older.
会被永久记录的
This could go on our permanent record.
我是你的继母 不能偷看我洗澡
I'm your stepmother. You are not supposed to be looking at me in the shower.
别告诉我爸
Don't tell my dad.
他会逼我退出运动队
He'll make me quit the sports team.
起来 起来
Get up. Get up.
他有麻烦了
He's in trouble.
必须惩罚你
You deserve a punishment.
短裤拉下来
Pull down your shorts.
后妈就是这样的吗
Is that what happens when you get a stepmom?
那可不合适啊
No way that's gonna fit in there.
滚出去 女人
Get out of there, girl!
他的手哪去了
Where did his hand go?
哎呀 -天哪
Ew! - Oh, my God!
没人亲过嘴
Nobody even kissed.
起码不是嘴
Yeah, not on their mouths at least.
我爹妈有个心肺复苏娃娃
My parents have a CPR doll.
我们可去练亲嘴
We can go practice kissing on that.
来吧
Come on.
超漂亮的心肺复苏娃娃
This is a really pretty CPR doll.
我先来
I guess I'll go first.
停
Stop.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
亲她
Kissing her.
未经允许 你不能乱亲
You can't kiss someone without their permission.
开过大会的 记得吗
Remember from assembly?
假装它是柏丽
Pretend it's Brixlee.
绅士点 -好
Try to be a gentleman. - Okay.
柏丽 我能亲你吗
Brixlee, can I kiss you?
为什么
Why?
为什么 -对
Why? - Yeah.
你喜欢我什么
What do you like about me?
那个
Well...
你很甜 你很好味
you're sweet. You smell good.
你也很聪明
You're smart, too.
你总帮推亨利的轮椅 尽管他超级损
You always push Henry in his wheelchair even though he's super mean.
滑板公园那次 我正想表白
And just when I think I've got you figured out,
但你玩滑板而经过
you go ahead and start skateboarding.
我同意了
I consent.
如何啊 -粘
How was it? - Sticky.
为什么她嘴里有毛发
Why does she have hair in her mouth?
知道吗 这没用
You know what? This isn't teaching us anything.
我们要看真人亲嘴
We need to see real people kissing.
只有这样 才知对错
That's the only way to know if we're doing it right.
我邻居是纵色狂
My neighbor is a total nymphomaniac.
她男友总是换
Her boyfriend's always over.
她纵火?
She starts fires?
不 她不纵火 她纵色 女色魔的意思
No, that's a pyromaniac. She's a nymphomaniac.
海陆双响炮喔
Someone who has sex on land and sea.
不会吧
Seriously?
本想明天给你惊喜
Okay, I was gonna wait till tomorrow to surprise you,
要不告诉你吧
but can I just tell you?
不 不用 -不 你想知道的
Nah, I'm good. - No, you want to know.
我什么都看不见
Ugh. I can barely see anything.
我们腻得不够多
I know we haven't been hanging out much,
因为自从我遇见本吉
you know, ever since I met Benji,
但我想弥补你
but I want to make it up to you.
所以明天我逃学
So, tomorrow, I'm skipping school,
我们开车进城看肯德里克·拉马尔演出
and we're driving to the city to see Kendrick Lamar.
闭嘴 -还要服用莫莉
Shut up! - And we're gonna do Molly.
你全都策划好了 -那当然
You thought of everything. - Of course I fucking have.
会很好玩的
It's gonna be amazing.
我来混音
Remix!
本吉给我们弄到了莫莉
Well, Benji got us the Molly.
本杰明 -谢谢
Benjamin. - Oh, thank you!
看
Look.
这不行 我们去爬树吧
This isn't working. Maybe we could go climb a tree.
不行 会被他们看见的
No, they'd see us.
我指的是纯爬树
No, I just meant let's go climb a tree.
兄弟 等等
Dude, wait.
我有个办法 能看他们亲嘴
I know a way we can see them kiss.
我不能
I can't.
上边有摄像头 全都能看到
It has a camera. We could see everything.
我们可以学技术
We can learn technique.
这是他爸工作用的 这不是玩具
It's for his dad's work. It's not a toy.
当然是玩具 玩具店有卖
Of course it's a toy. They sell it at toy stores.
我叔叔在部队驾驶无人机
My uncle flew a drone for the Army,
现在他睡梦里会大喊 还拉肚子
and now he yells in his sleep and has crazy diarrhea.
他居然把无人机留在家里 太糟了
It's messed up that he even keeps it in the house.
你每天都会路过无人机
You have to walk by it every day.
他在折磨你 -说的没错
He's torturing you. - It's true.
就像你表妹穿着比基尼走
It's like when your cousin walks around in a bikini
她还嘲笑你
and she taunts you.
如果你被发现 你会被禁足的
If he finds out, you'll be grounded.
你再也去不了索伦家了
You won't be able to go to Soren's.
更惨的是 你爸不再信你了
And even worse, you'll lose your father's trust.
说的也没错
It's true, too.
她只爱你的本性
She'll love you for who you are.
对 猥琐亲嘴者 还记得之前的毛片吗
Yeah, a shitty kisser. Remember the porn from earlier?
那家伙都不懂亲嘴
That guy didn't even know how to kiss.
他舔那女人的屁眼
He was just licking that woman's asshole.
你想亲屁眼吗 麦克斯 -绝不
You want to kiss an asshole, Max? - No.
麦克斯 别听他的 他想去 因为他迷上了万人迷
Max, don't listen to him. He just wants to go because he's obsessed with popular boys.
相信我 麦克斯
Believe me, Max.
不懂亲嘴的话 你不会想去索伦家的
You don't want to go to Soren's not knowing how to kiss.
等明天你们两女生腻完之后
So, tomorrow, after you get some girl time,
不如腻我这个男生
why don't you come over for some man time?
不 说了这周末我要和莉莉出去玩
No, I told you I'm hanging out with Lily this weekend.
对 我很难不见你 因为你是我最好的朋友
Yeah, it's just... you know, it's hard for me not to see you, 'cause you're my best friend.
但莉莉是我最好的朋友
But Lily's my best friend.
明白 非常明白
Yeah, I get it. Totally, totally get it.
我还是找前任玛格丽特玩得了
I'll probably just hang out with my ex, Margaret.
你想我嫉妒吗
Are you trying to make me jealous?
没有啊 为什么 你嫉妒吗
Uh, no. Why? Are you jealous?
这招没用
Yeah, this isn't working out.
我知道你自觉不够辣 所以没信心
I know. You're not hot enough to be acting like this,
下次你寻思 好男人都去了哪儿
so the next time that you're wondering where all the nice guys went,
记住 你现在放跑了一个好男人
ber that you let one walk right out the door.
什么
What?
我什么都没说
I didn't say anything.
我再也不想见你了
I never want to see you again.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
等等 那小子去哪儿了
Wait, where'd the guy go?
谁管 女生在抱抱
Who cares? The girls just hugged.
她们肯定会亲的
They are definitely gonna kiss.
更近一点
We might need to get closer.
你听到没有
Do you hear that?
那是什么
What is that?
在监视我们
It's fucking spying on us.
好 轮到我飞了 -给我
All right, it's my turn to fly. - Give it!
我想吵吵她们 -不
I just want to buzz 'em. - No!
会被你弄坏的
Hey, you're gonna break it.
你想要吗 好
You want it? Fine!
惨了
Shit!
不
No!
妈的 见鬼 索尔 -我们两个都有错
Shit! What the hell, Thor? - That was both of our faults.
我爸会杀了我 现在怎么办
Well, Dad's gonna kill me. What do I do now?
搞什么鬼
Whoa! - What the hell?!
就说有人闯入 -什么
We say there was a break-in. - What...?
他们捣毁了这里 拿走了无人机
They trashed the place and took the drone.
有史以来最傻的想法
That's the most stupid fucking idea I've ever heard!
兄弟们
Guys, guys.
我们只需去那边
All we have to do is just go over there
说出实话 上帝会支持我们的
and tell the truth, then God will be on our side.
嗨 有事吗
Hey. Can I help you?
确实有事 姐姐
Uh, I hope so, madam.
我们在用无人机跟踪乌龟一家
We were using our drone to follow a family of turtles,
无人机可能坠毁在你家后院
and we thought it might have crashed in your backyard.
没错 它在这里 快进来
Oh, yeah, yeah, it's here. Come on in.
你们喜欢乌龟吗 -是
So, you guys like turtles? - Yeah.
太棒了 -时间到 混蛋
That's awesome. - Time's up, motherfuckers.
妈的 是陷阱
Shit! It's a trap.
你以为我会在乎什么乌龟?
You think I give a fuck about turtles?
对不起 我们只想学亲嘴
We're sorry. We just wanted to learn how to kiss.
卢卡斯 这与她们无关
Lucas, it's none of their business.
我们该说真话
We should have just told the truth.
我们要去亲嘴趴
We're going to a kissing party,
我们谁也没有亲过 我们怕
and none of us have ever kissed, and we're scared.
妈的 卢卡斯
Goddamn it, Lucas.
我做过爱 但我没有亲过女人
I've had sex before, but I've never kissed a girl.
上网 输入"如何亲嘴"即可
Just go online and type in "how to kiss."
人尽皆知
That's what everyone does.
这很容易
It's very easy.
能把无人机还我们吗
Look, can we please have the drone back?
天雷滚滚号 是我爸的
It's a BD Rolling Thunder. It's my dad's.
他工作上用的 能还我吗
He needs it for work. Can I please have it back?
我很需要它 拜托 -没有的事
I really need it. Please. - I don't think so.
如果不还 我告诉我爸是你们偷的
If you don't give it back, I'll tell my dad you stole it.
我告诉他你是变态
And I'll tell him that you're a pervert.
还要告诉全校
We'll tell the whole school.
这是性骚扰
This is sensual harassment.
还要昭告天下 说你厌女
We'll tell everyone that you're a misogynist.
我没按摩过谁
I never massaged anyone.
(按摩/厌女 同音)
你不尊重女性 就会这样
This is what happens when you don't respect women.
我尊重女人 我妈是我最好的朋友
I respect women. My mom's my best friend.
那我呢
What about me?
天哪 这下我死定了
Oh, God, I'm so fucked.
我爸会杀了我
My dad's gonna kill me.
你非要偷窥她们 好一个女权主义者
You had to snoop on them. You're such a feminist.
我不是女权主义者 我爱女人
I'm-I'm not a feminist. I love women.
我父母肯定会通知你父母
And my parents are definitely gonna call your guys' parents.
我们都会被禁足
We're all gonna get grounded.
忘了索伦的趴吧 我们完了
Forget Soren's party. We're fucked.
你笑什么 都怪你
Why are you smiling? This is actually your fault.
这是战利品
This is leverage.
宾果
Bingo.
这什么 -我不知道
What is it? - I have no idea.
卫生棉条
That's a tampon.
干什么用的 -女人塞屁股的 防止婴儿掉出来
What's it for? - Girls shove it up their buttholes to stop babies from coming out.
某八年级生告诉我的
An eighth-grader told me that.
人体真是迷
The human body is truly a mystery.
她们居然还在吃口香糖
Can't believe they still eat chewables.
软糖好吃多了
The gummies are so much better.
我喜欢口香糖 给我一个
I like the chewables. I want one.
操蛋的防儿童开启瓶盖
Fucking childproof bullshit!
索尔 索尔 索尔
Thor! Thor! Thor! Thor! Thor! Thor!
是那俩女人
It's the girls.
喂
Hello?
你拿走了我包 里面有我的驾照和手机
You took my bag. It has my license, my phone.
马上还给我
Bring it back right now.
你少叽歪 把无人机还我
Fuck that noise. I want my drone back.
交给我
I got this. I got this, I got this.
你刚说什么 小王八蛋
What did you just say, you little bitch?
我要扯烂你的喉咙
I'll take a shit down your throat.
你为什么这嗓音
Why are you talking like that?
汉娜 我家有小弟
Hannah, I have a little brother.
就该吓吓他们 -你吓到我了
You're supposed to scare them. - Well, you scared me.
我们就想教训你们
Listen, we-we were just trying to teach you a lesson.
无人机肯定会还给你
I promise you we were gonna give the drone back.
不可能 她们还会骗我们
No way. They could trick us again.
或用暴力
Or overpower us.
天哪 万一他们拿走莫莉
Oh, my God. What if they take the Molly?
那我们就没办法吃了
Then we wouldn't be able to take it.
不 他们是孩子 会死的
No, they're children. They would die.
我是刚才的麦克斯
This is Max from earlier.
明早7:40 约翰亚当斯对面操场见
Meet us at the playground across from John Adams tomorrow at 7:40 a.m.
带上无人机 别糊弄精豆小子
Bring the drone, and don't fuck with the Bean Bag Boys.
很强势 -超级强势
That was tough. - Very tough.
对付那俩娘们 我很硬
I kind of got a boner talking to those girls.
电话还没挂
We're still on the phone.
妈的 妈的 -搞屁啊
Shit! Fuck, fuck. - What the shit?!
六 七 八 九 十
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
十一 十二 ...十五
11, 12, 13, 14, 15...
别再靠近
Don't come any closer.
为什么 -因为你们很暴力
Why? - 'Cause you could overpower us.
无人机放在地上 从100倒数
So, put the drone on the slide, and count back from a hundred,
闭上眼睛
and close your eyes.
别玩阴的
And don't try anything funny.
有目击者
There are witnesses.
好 我们要开长途
Okay, we have a long drive ahead of us,
把包给我们 不然弄死你们
so give us the bag or I will hurt you.
别测试我
Do not test me.
威胁没好处的 农民
Threats will get you nowhere, peasant.
把莫莉给我们
Just give us the fucking Molly!
好 谁是莫莉 因为她不和我们一起
Okay. Who's Molly? 'Cause she's not with us.
弟弟们
Guys.
莫莉是性药 新闻有曝光的
Molly is a sex drug. Dateline did an exposé on it.
你竟敢把药带到我们的操场
You had us bring drugs to a fucking playground?!
这里全是孩子
There are children here!
妈的 -没事的
Shit. - It's okay.
我知道分寸
I know what to do.
逮捕你们
We're making a citizen's arrest!
你们都被捕了
You're both under arrest!
趴到地上 -老天爷
Get on the ground! - Sweet Jesus.
快快快 -别动
Up, up, up! - Stay still!
手举起来 -别动
Hands up! Hands up! - Stay still!
马上趴下
Get down now! Get down now!
你这是在假装装子弹吗
Did you just reload your fake gun?
你在嘲笑我吗 -举起手来
Are you mocking me? - Put your hands up!
你在嘲笑我吗
Are you mocking me?!
你所说的都会对你不利 -是法庭上
Anything will be used against you that you say. - In court.
你才是手里有药的人
You know, you're the one holding drugs,
为什么不逮捕你
so why don't I do a citizen's arrest on you?
操
Fuck.
超时了 爆头
Time-out, crackheads.
天哪
Oh, my God.
取消计划 不能让她们带走毒品
Deal's off. We can't let them put drugs back on the street.
那些烂瘾君子
Look at those dirty fucking junkies.
薄命红颜
Their lives are already ruined.
把毒品给她们 取回无人机
Let's just give them the drugs and get the drone.
也许还有办法
Maybe there's a way we can
保护我们的地盘 取回无人机
protect our community and get the drone back.
拖延她们
Stall them.
这些毒品 你们打算怎么办
So, what do you plan to do with those drugs, huh?
拿走去爽一爽
Take 'em and feel amazing.
她们是瘾君子
They're addicts.
嗯
Yeah.
你吸了一辈子毒吗
So, you been drugging your whole life?
嗯哼 -没错
Uh-huh. - E'r'day.
好
Oh. Nice.
他在干什么
What's he doing? Hey.
爽 -果然有用
Yes! Yes! - It's working!
果然有用 -爽
It's working! - Yes!
飞到学校去
Fly it to the school!
往树飞去了 小心
You're heading for the trees! Watch out!
我们会成功的
We're gonna make it! We're gonna make it!
干
Fuck!
算那些女人走运 没踢她们屁股
Those girls are lucky I didn't kick their asses.
我好了 被她们找到了
Oh, no! They found us!
该死 -她们在学校
Oh, shit. - They're on school property.
她们才不管 她们毒瘾发了
They don't care. They're tweaking.
需要找谁
You know who we need?
不要去说 -搞得我们像鲁蛇
No, don't say it. - We'll look like losers.
千万别说 -反霸凌联盟
Don't say it. Don't say it. - SCAB!
闭嘴 -反霸凌联盟
Shut up. - SCAB!
闭嘴 -卢卡斯 闭嘴
Shut up. Zip it. - Lucas, shut up.
反霸凌联盟 -那是什么
SCAB! - What is that?
有三个男生有危险
There's three boys in danger!
我们怕 反霸凌联盟 来救我们
We're scared! SCAB, help us!
我们没事
We're okay.
我们不怕 我们很好 -卢卡斯 闭嘴
We're not scared. We're... we're fine. - Lucas, shut up.
只管进学校
Just walking into school.
普通的日子 -上帝啊
Average day. - Jesus Christ.
霸凌不可饶
Bullying is wack.
走上正轨
Get on the right track.
霸凌不可饶
Bullying is wack.
走上正轨
Get on the right track.
霸凌不可饶
Bullying is wack.
走上正轨
Get on the right track.
霸凌不可饶
Bullying is wack.
攻击我们一人
When you attack one of us,
等于攻击我们所有人
you attack all of us.
你的软弱 给了我们力量
Your weakness gives us strength.
那三小子偷了我的包 -今天不行 恶霸
Well, those kids stole my bag. - Not today, bully!
今天不行
Not today.
搞什么 -霸凌不可饶
What the fuck? - Bullying is wack.
走上正轨
Get on the right track.
我人生中最美好的一天
This is the best day of my life.
走上正轨
Get on the right track.
别担心 过后再找
Don't worry, we'll find them later.
反霸凌联盟 刚在照片墙标签了我们
SCAB just tagged us on Instagram.
之前是奶嘴娃 现在这个
First Sippy Cup, and now this?
我六年级两星期了 我是社交大鳄
I'm two weeks into sixth grade, I'm already a social piranha.
兄弟们 我爸五点回来
Guys, my dad gets back at 5:00.
如果届时没有新无人机 我会被禁足
If we don't get a new drone by then, I'm grounded.
你们也会被禁足 意思玩不成趴了
Which means we're all grounded, which means no party,
也就没有柏丽
which means no Brixlee.
一辈子的奶嘴娃 -没有柏丽
Sippy Cup for life. - No Brixlee,
没有朋友 没有希望
no friends, no hope,
父母吵架 只能待在自己屋里
parents fighting, trapped in our rooms,
独自一人 每星期二吃两份卷饼
all alone, two Taco Tuesdays.
那么 麦克斯 怎么办
So, Max, what are we gonna do?
翘课去搞新无人机
We're gonna ditch school and get a new drone.
别用下半身思考 麦克斯
Stop thinking with your big old dick, Max.
会被永久记录在案
That could go on our permanent record.
麦克斯的下半身 指引着正确的方向
Max's big old dick is pointing us in the right direction.
谢谢 如果有人亲柏丽 我会死的
Thank you. If anyone else kisses Brixlee, I'll die.
等等 我有个计划
Wait, what? Here's the plan.
我带啤酒去索伦家
I'm gonna bring a beer to Soren's,
我啜啤酒 于是所有人都会知道
and I'm gonna sip that beer so everyone will know...
你是个酒鬼
That you're an alcoholic.
肯定会很棒 -兄弟们
That would be great. - Guys.
北角画廊才有无人机卖
The only place around here that has one is at North Point Galleria.
四英里远
That's four miles away.
四英里 怎么搞
Four miles? How the fuck are we getting four miles?
你有优步 -不 会被转到我妈手机上 她会知道
You have Uber. - No, it goes directly to my mom's phone. She'll know.
那自行车
Then we bike.
你哪有钱买新无人机
Where are you even gonna get the money for a new drone?
干嘛 -你懂的
What? - You know.
我们的超级万智牌 没门
Our Turzan of Uzkara card? No way!
你说这张牌超屌的
You said everyone wants to buy it.
这是我们三个的
We got it together.
那就算我们联合出售 作为朋友
And we're gonna sell it together, as friends.
来吧 卢卡斯
Come on, Lucas.
精豆小子 做什么都一起上
Bean Bag Boys do everything together.
好
Okay.
还挺有道理
Guess that makes sense.
太好了
Yes! - Yes!
卢卡斯 永远的精豆小子 -是
Lucas! Bean Bag Boys for life. - Yeah!
我们超屌的
We're being so bad.
我们超屌 我们超屌
♪ We're bad, we're so bad ♪
我们超屌
♪ We're bad, we're so bad. ♪
我要丢掉这些药
I need to get rid of these drugs.
你在做什么 -丢掉毒品
What are you doing?! - Getting rid of the drugs!
我刚想扔到溪里
I'm just gonna throw them in the stream.
水会被污染的
It can contaminate the water.
那就扔到林子里去
Well, then we can throw it in the forest.
这是性药
It's a sex drug.
万一被狐狸吃了 去干松鼠呢
What if a fox eats it and tries to fuck a squirrel?
会要它的命
It'll kill him.
那怎么处理
Well, then how do we get rid of drugs?
类似处理宝宝
The same way we get rid of a baby.
流产 -收养?
Abortion? - Adoption?
不
No.
去商场路上 送到消防队
We drop it off at the firehouse on our way up to the mall.
好主意
That's a really good idea.
看来有人出价了
Ah. I just got a bite on our card.
好 把我地址给他们
Nice. Give 'em my address.
我父母不在家 我有最好的零食
My parents aren't home, and I have the best snacks.
彼得潘69 五分钟后来买卡
PeterPan69 is gonna be here in five minutes to buy the card.
好 准备一下
Well, let's get ready.
我在爹妈壁橱里发现很多武器
I found all of these weapons in the back of my parents' closet.
为什么要武器
I still don't get why we need weapons.
他可能是恋童癖
He could be a pedophile.
但他不能骚扰我们三人
He can't molest all three of us.
他只需要一人
All he needs is one.
(肛门珠)
铝制珠?
"An-al beads"?
又名双节棍 混蛋
Aka nunchucks, motherfucker.
这不是玩具
Yeah! - It's not a toy.
惨
Oh, shoot.
一股屎味
They smell like shit.
嗨 我在找卢卡斯
Hello. Uh, I'm looking for Lucas.
是我 -我是克劳德
That's me. - I'm Claude.
嗨
Hey.
那是我妈
That's my mom back there.
你好
Hi-ya!
废话少说 你是恋童癖吗
Let's cut the shit. Are you a pedophile?
什么 不
What? No.
卢卡斯 如果你是恋童癖
Lucas, if you were a pedophile
站在三个单身男孩前 你会承认吗
standing in front of three single boys, would you admit it?
可能不会
Probably not.
那他为什么要承认
Then why would he?
拜托
Oh, come on.
我像恋童癖吗
Do I look like a pedophile?
像 -绝对 -百分之千
Sure do. - Yes, absolutely. - 1,000%.
不像话
That's not fair.
你比谁都像恋童癖
You look more like a pedophile than anyone I've ever seen.
我不是恋童癖 我是好人
Look, I'm not a pedophile. I'm a cool guy.
好 你可以进来 但请脱鞋
Fine. You can come in, but please take your shoes off.
我找遍全世界求这张卡
You know, I've searched the world for this.
你为什么带彩弹枪
Why are you bringing the paintball gun?
万一有人敢搞我们
In case anyone fucks with us.
这张卡很精致
This card is exquisite.
你怎么弄到的 -那个夏天我搬家
How'd you get it? - The summer I moved here,
我 麦克斯和索尔 开始洗狗
me, Max and Thor started a dog-washing business.
我们赚了八块钱 用钱买了卡牌增强包 内含这张卡
We earned eight bucks, and we used the money to buy an Ascension pack, and this card was in it.
你很幸运
Well, you got very lucky.
真正幸运是遇见麦克斯和索尔
The real luck was meeting Max and Thor.
非常好
Fascinating.
我们开始自称为精豆小子
We started calling ourself the Bean Bag Boys.
知道为什么吗 -因为你们小而弥坚
You know why? - Because you had some beanbags?
没错 -天才
That's right. - Yeah. Genius.
成交
You got yourself a deal.
来吧 达成交易
Let's go. Let's make it happen.
不 我不能
No, I can't do this.
对不起
Sorry.
卢卡斯 给我过来
Lucas, get your butt over here right now.
不好意思 12岁孩子就这么干吗
Excuse me, is this how all 12-year-olds conduct business?
怎么回事
What the hell just happened?
我以为你同意的
I thought you were cool with this.
你说只要有一个人不同意 我们就不干
You said we wouldn't do this if one of us wasn't on board.
我不同意 -你在乎什么
I'm not on board. - Why do you care so much?
为什么不在乎
Why don't you care?
这张卡充满了回忆
This card has a lot of memories,
你就为了亲普通女生而卖掉这张卡吗
and you're just gonna throw it all away because you want to kiss some basic girl?
野蛮人
Savage.
柏丽不是普通女生
Brixlee isn't just some girl.
我们很可能会结婚
We're probably gonna get married.
每段婚姻都以离婚告终
Every marriage ends in divorce.
卢卡斯 你出局了
Lucas, you're outvoted.
你先息怒
Listen, I can tell you're lashing out with anger,
但柏丽可能是我一生挚爱
but Brixlee is probably the love of my life.
对不起 太太 我能喝杯水吗
Excuse me, ma'am. Can I get a glass of water, please?
你好
Hello?
兄弟们
Hey, guys?
她有什么幕后故事
What can you tell me about her backstory?
她从哪儿来
Where is she supposed to be from?
很有异国情调
She seems quite exotic.
给我听好了
Okay, listen carefully,
因为我只说一遍
'cause I'll make this offer only once.
400块 转让给我
400 bucks to take her off your hands.
不 550美元
No. We need 550, U.S.
滚了 什么啊
Fuck off. What?
那是我全部零用钱
That's my entire allowance.
听着 克劳德 废话少说
Listen, Claude, let's just cut the bullshit.
我是女商人之子 大家没意见吧
I'm the son of a businesswoman, and I think we both know,
如果你不想买娃娃
if you didn't want to buy the doll,
你早就走了
you would've left already.
别把我们当孩子 我们懂生意经
Stop treating us like kids. We know how things work.
买不买心肺复苏娃
So, do you want to buy the CPR doll or not?
傻子们 我本来想付1000的
Fools. I'd have paid a thousand.
有没有人感觉他要干娃娃
Anyone else feel like he's gonna fuck that doll?
该补充水分
We should hydrate.
骑了14分钟有了
We've been biking for almost 14 minutes straight.
从未离家这么远
I don't think I've ever been this far from home.
我在这里想出了"猫"的旋律
I think I did a production of Cats around here.
你真不再唱了吗
You're really not gonna sing anymore?
对 从来没这么高兴过
Yeah. I've never been happier.
把药给我们 -干
Just give us the drugs. - Fuck.
你怎么找到我们的
How'd you find us?
她的手机有跟踪程序
Her phone.They tracked us.
不会给你们的
We're not giving you these drugs.
要交给消防队
We're giving them to firefighters.
去喊人吧
Get help.
走 -我们开的是汽车 傻小子
Go! - We're in a car, dipshits.
跑不过我们的
You're not gonna outrun us.
我们骑的是超速自行车 呆子
Not on my fast bike, nerds.
有本事开车过来 鲁蛇
Good luck getting your car in here, losers!
妈的
Shit.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
你别想拿回药
You're not getting these drugs back!
把性药给她
Just give her the sex drugs!
分头走
Peel off!
我不会让你毁了你的...
I won't let you destroy your li...
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你没事吧 -卢卡斯 你没事吧
Are you okay? - Lucas, are you okay?
怎么回事
What the hell happened?
我们要逃离保姆 她想摸我们的老二
We were running away from our babysitter 'cause she was trying to touch our penises.
他们在瞎说
What? That is not true.
没瞎说 -是瞎说 -我没有
Yes, it is. - Yes, it is. - I wasn't.
你就是的 -我没有
Yeah, you were. - I wasn't...
走走走 -又怎么了
Go, go, go, go, go! Go, go! - What happened?
走 走
Go, go!
卢卡斯 你没事吧
Lucas, are you okay?
应该没事
I-I think I'm fine.
你的手臂 -不
Your arm. - Oh, hell no.
我打911
Yo, I'm-a call 911.
救命 -不不不 没事的
Help! Help! - No, no, no. It's okay.
经常这样
This happens all the time.
我们得走了
Come on, we got to go. We got to go. Go.
救命 -我们得... 快
Help! Ow! - We got... Come on.
我去拿自行车
I'll get the bikes.
好 我把她们的手机扔进了灌木丛
Okay. I threw their phone in a prickle bush.
所以她们不能再追踪我们了
So they can't track us anymore.
好痛
Oh, the pain!
卢卡斯 你必须安静
Lucas, you have to be quiet.
有冰块吗
Okay, do we have any ice?
没有 我们在马路上
No, we're in a fucking alley.
止痛药有没有
What about pain medication?
我们有莫莉 可以给他 -不
We have the Molly we can give him. - No!
也对 以防他想操我们
Yeah, he's probably just gonna try and have sex with us.
叫救护车
Call an ambulance!
任务结束 -我们会被逮捕的
Mission's over! - We'll get busted.
此外 你有保险吗 -我不知道
Plus, do you even have insurance? - I don't know.
你呢 - 我不知道
Do you? - I don't know.
我只有免赔额 -那就行
I think I only have a deductible. - It's all right.
格斗场上很常见
This happens to MMA fighters all the time.
用你的手撞硬物 可以复位
We just got to ram your arm into something very hard so it pops back in place.
好 妈的 那就来吧
Fine! Fuck it! Let's just get this over with.
来吧 -放松
Come on. - Easy. All right.
一二三
One, two, three.
手臂错了
Wrong arm!
好 重新开局 -好
Okay, new site, new site. - Okay.
你躺下 把手臂给我
Okay, lie down on your back and give me your arm.
快
Come on.
上面写着接下来有点痛
All right. It says this next part's gonna hurt,
你该咬硬物
that you should bite down on something hard.
我有办法
I know.
张嘴 给
Open. There you go.
好
Okay.
数到三 -一
On three. - One,
二 三
two, three.
刚收到泰勒的短信 -她说什么
Just got a text from Taylor. - What'd she say?
她想知道 你怎么没在学校
She wants to know why you aren't in school
如果你今晚要参趴
and if you're coming to the party tonight.
那就回复
Just write...
对不起一二三
Okay, sorry. One, two, three!
我来帮忙
Let me help, let me help.
注意 数到三 -一
Focus! On three. - One!
二 三
Two! Three!
没想到真的有用
Wow. I didn't think that'd actually work.
你会好的
You're gonna be good, man.
不
No.
我不太好
I'm really not.
我父母要离婚
My parents are getting a divorce.
你做了什么
What'd you do?
索尔 -什么
Thor! - What?
对不起
Sorry.
我爸要搬出去
My dad's moving out.
不管你父母之间如何
Whatever happens between your parents,
精豆小子永远支持你
you always got the Bean Bag Boys.
我们绝不分开 永远的精豆小子
We'll never split up. Bean Bag Boys for life.
保证吗
You promise?
保证 -保证
Promise. - Promise.
来吧
Come on.
给你去买儿童泰诺
Let's get you some Children's Tylenol.
需要帮忙吗  -不 我能行
Want some help, buddy? - No, I got it.
还是你来吧
Okay, just do it.
嗨 迈尔斯 -嗨 老兄
Hey, Miles. - Hey, man.
上班还是下班 -刚连上了三班
Coming in or coming off? - Just got off a triple.
现在就算有人抢我 我都不在乎
Man, I don't care if I get mugged.
我今天不想打字了
I'm not typing up any more paperwork today.
警察
Cop.
惨了 我们手-里-有-药
Shit. We have D-R-U-G-S on us.
他懂拼写 你正常一点
He knows how to spell. Just act normal.
假装说话 -说什么
Pretend to talk. - About what?
正常点
Just be normal.
你对政治有什么看法
What do you think about politics?
说来复杂
It's a complicated issue.
这个警察很怪
This cop's acting weird.
他在目奸我们
He's eye-fucking us.
正常一点 笑一笑
Just act normal. Just laugh.
我们是爱笑的傻小子
We're just two cool guys laughing.
我们逃学了
We skipped school.
卢卡斯
Lucas!
我们有麻烦了吗
Are we in trouble?
通常我会上报
Yeah, well, usually, I'd call this in,
但鉴于你们的诚实
but because you were honest with me,
就放你们一马
I'm gonna let you slide, all right?
下不为例 好吗
Just promise not to do it again, okay?
我们保证 谢谢 警官
We promise. Thank you, sir.
好
All right.
差一点
That was a close one.
等等 索尔在哪
Wait, where's Thor?
等等
Hold it.
过来
Come here.
你裤子里有什么
What do you have in your pants?
我的老二
My penis.
拉出来
Pull it out.
我也有个大家伙
I also have a big dick.
放回去 我今天很宽容
Put it back. I'm being generous today.
我们也有毒品 -老弟
We also have drugs. - Dude!
他在目奸我们 -好 你有什么
He was onto us. - Okay, what do you have?
附表一 受管制药
Schedule I controlled substance,
意图发放
with intent to distribute.
这些是维生素 好吗
Brother, these are vitamins, okay?
儿童维生素
Children's vitamins, at that.
不 那些是毒品 -看啊
No, those are drugs. - No, look.
如果这是毒品 那这也是毒品
If that's drugs, then this is drugs, too.
如果你不逮捕我们 我举报你 -卢卡斯
If you don't arrest us, I'll report you. - Lucas!
少他妈管我
Just leave me the fuck alone!
不好意思 对孩子爆粗口 但他妈的
I mean, sorry to fucking swear at kids, but fuck.
我要逮捕你 因为你他妈毁了我一天
You know, I'm gonna arrest you for fucking ruining my day.
药我没收了 让我回家
All right? I'll take them. Let me go home!
他在呼叫支援 -怎么办
He's calling for backup. - What do we do?
听我说 我决定不要孩子
Hello. Listen. I've decided I don't want kids.
怎么了 -警察在目奸我们
What's up? - The cop's eye-fucking us.
我们得跑 我知道该怎么做
We have to make a run for it. I know what to do.
不 不 无需讨论
Well, no, it's not up for discu...
也许你是侦探
Well, yeah, well, no, you may be detective,
但在婚姻中 我们是平等的
but in the marriage we're equal.
啥
Wha...?
挂电话 谁在乎啊
Just hang up. Who cares?
这免费 因为我是警察
This is free 'cause I'm a cop.
什么鬼 索尔
What the fuck, Thor?
你都不关心我肩膀
You didn't even care about my shoulder.
你只想啤酒 -我能一心两用
You just wanted a beer. - I can care about two things.
对 你和你的蠢啤酒
Yeah, you and your stupid beer!
现在我们是逃犯了 -你对我喊什么
Now we're fugitives! - Why are you yelling at me?
我抛下了祖传自行车就跑了
I just ran off without my family's bikes.
两轮周末搞砸了 -兄弟们
Cycle Sundays are fucked! - Guys, guys.
商场
The mall!
我们到了
Yes! Yes! - Yes! - We made it!
快来
Come on, come on, come on.
该死 -妈哟
Oh, shit. - Holy mother...
祖宗的
Goddamn it!
好极
Great.
前有高速 后有警察
Now we're trapped between a highway and the authorities.
目前的处境
Well, we wouldn't be in this position right now
全都怪你痴颠
if you weren't such a narc.
兄弟们 商场就在那儿
Guys, the mall's right there.
过高速公路就行
All we have to do is cross the highway,
车流都没动
and the cars aren't even moving.
我们是五年 还是六年级生
Now, are we fifth-graders, or are we sixth-graders?
我要回树林
Well, I'm going back into the woods.
我靠雨水和松鼠而活
I'll live off of rainwater and squirrels.
我不干了
I don't give a fuck.
不 你别去
Uh, no, you won't.
天哪 -不 不
Oh, my gosh! - No, no.
就像停车场 看
It's-it's like a parking lot, see?
等等 你有偷第二瓶啤酒
Wait! You stole another beer?
搞屁啦 索尔
What the fuck, Thor? - Hey.
你们会是那些
You guys aren't the ones who's gonna have
墓碑写着"奶嘴娃"的人
"Sippy Cup" on their goddamn tombstone!
天哪 说就说 别乱喷
God. Say it, don't spray it.
离开高速公路
Get off the freeway!
儿童过境
Children crossing.
儿童过境 -下高速去
Please, children are crossing. - Get off the road.
你们在干什么 到边上去 -走
What are you guys doing? Get back to the side. - Go!
走走走 走 -现在 -白痴
Go, go, go, go. - Now. - Fucking idiots!
等等 有短信
Wait. I got a message.
是泰勒发的
Oh, it's from Taylor.
她说马库斯要来参趴
She said Marcus is coming to the party.
他很迷柏丽
He has a huge crush on Brixlee.
她肯定会亲他的
She's definitely gonna kiss him.
他是年级最优生 -等等
He's the nicest kid in our grade. - Wait, wait.
我才是年级最优生
I'm the nicest kid in our grade.
按顺序是我 马库斯 麦克斯 你
It goes me, Marcus, Max, you.
我比麦克斯好 -不 你没有
I'm way nicer than Max. - No, you're not!
你去年让威洛比老师哭了
You made Ms. Willoughby cry last year.
她已经在哭 我不过是拍了照
Hey, she was already crying. I just took her picture.
兄弟们 兄弟们 看
Guys, guys! Look!
车子动了 -惨了
It started. - Oh, shit.
妈的 -妈的
Shit. - Oh, fuck.
我们回去吧 -回去
Let's go back! - Let's go back!
我们被困住了
We're trapped.
让我们下去
Let us out!
要死了 我要死了
I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die.
我们不会死 等一下就好 好吗 -妈的
No, we're not. We just need to time it, okay? - Oh, fuck!
只需要时间 -该死
We just need to time it right. - Shit!
兄弟们 我们能行
We can do this, guys. We can do this!
不
N-No!
麦克斯 不 -你疯了吗
Max, no! - Are you batshit crazy?!
你到底在干什么
What the fuck are you doing?!
该死 他成功了
Oh, shit. He made it. - Oh!
我成功了
I did it!
卢卡斯 卢卡斯 现在看我
Lucas, Lucas, look at me right now.
我知道你很怕
I know you're scared.
我一点也不
I'm not, at all...
闭嘴 索尔
Shut up, Thor!
卢卡斯 操 不 -该死
Lucas, fuck you! No! - Shit! Shit!
卢卡斯
Lucas!
不 卢卡斯
No! Lucas!
我没死
I'm not dead!
我没有死 -好
I'm not dead! - All right.
你快过来 -是
You got it, man. Come on. - Yes! Yes!
去死 -我也爱你
Fuck you! - I love you, too.
现在 过来
Now, come over here.
我想妈妈
I want my mom.
快 快 -来吧
Come on. Come on. - Come on.
我很好 我就住在这里
I'm fine. I'll just live here.
我很好 -来吧
I-I'm good. - Come on!
快 -你能行的
Come on! - You got this!
好 来吧 索尔
All right. Come on, Thor.
你不是奶嘴娃 你超屌
You are not Sippy Cup. You're a badass.
快点 快点
Come on, come on!
我的啤酒
Oh, shit! My beer!
喔 妈呀
Oh, shit!
等一下
Oh! - Oh, wait.
那是我爸的心肺复苏娃
That's my dad's CPR doll.
我爸的心肺复苏娃
Oh. - That's my dad's CPR doll!
我们不是杀人犯 -好
We're not murderers! - Yes!
我们得救了 -我们不是杀人犯
We're saved! - We're not fucking killers!
我们不是杀手 -好耶
We're not killers! - Yes!
不好意思 -借过
Pardon me. - Excuse me.
不好意思
Pardon me. Sorry. - Hey!
抱歉 借过
Excuse me. Got to get through.
抱歉
Sorry.
我们打过电话来 关于天雷滚滚
Hey. We called about the BD Rolling Thunder.
对不起你们了
I'm so sorry, you guys.
已经卖了
Sold it.
你真会开玩笑
Ha-ha. Nice joke.
太好笑了
So funny.
我真的卖了 卖给两个姑娘 说她们认识你
No, I did. I sold it. Two girls, said they knew you.
去死
Fuck you!
天哪 -我要杀了你全家 他们会... -糖吃多了吧
Jesus. - I'm gonna kill your family, and then they're gonna come alive... - Ease off the sugar, huh?
把你全家变成僵尸 -麦克斯
...and turn your whole family into zombies! - Max!
我刚想说 我还没说完
I was gonna say... you didn't let me finish...
她们留了纸条
they left a note for you.
这样走路什么意思
Why are they walking like that?
我不知道
I don't know.
你们是怎么追踪我们的
How'd you guys track us?
我们把包扔进灌木丛
We threw your bag in prickle bushes.
笨蛋 你自己说 没有天雷滚滚号 你就完了
Dumbass, you told us that your life would be over if you didn't get a BD Rolling Thunder,
这家店 儿童骑车最远到此了 -好
and this is the only place a child could get to on a tricycle. - Okay.
我有药 无人机给我
I have the drugs. Now give me the drone.
开什么玩笑
Are you fucking kidding me?
这什么鬼 软糖维生素而已
What in the actual fuck? These are just gummy vitamins.
妈的 -早就说她会检查
Shit. - Told you she was gonna check.
操 -莫莉呢
Fuck. - Where is the Molly?
在哪儿 -警察拿了
Where is it? - A cop has it.
你把药给了警察
You gave our drugs to a cop?
等下 听着
Wait. Look.
我知道你不认识我们
I know you don't know us
认为我们是傻小子
and you think we're just stupid kids,
但听我说
but just listen to me.
不管你们有什么问题
Whatever problems you're having,
吃药不是答案
drugs are not the answer.
毒品只能给你虚假的现实感
Drugs just give you a false sense of reality.
也许你自认生活糟糕
You may think your lives are bad,
但你有家人和朋友爱你
but you have family and friends who love you.
你能闭嘴吗
Can you shut the fuck up?
我刚花了600买了无人机
I just spent $600 on a fucking drone.
你毁了我的激情演讲
You ruined my passionate moment.
太蠢了 -今天算是完了
Well, it was stupid. - This day is fucked.
只有本吉手里有莫莉
Benji is the only one who has Molly,
他不会卖给我们的
and he won't sell it to us.
我好抱歉
Okay. Well, I'm sorry.
我们完了
We're fucked.
交给我们 我们去拿回药
We'll do it. We'll get your drugs.
鬼才去 -你又在干什么
The fuck we will. - What the hell, dude?
他会卖药给儿童吗
Do you think he would sell to kids?
我们不是儿童
We're not kids.
我们是少年
We're tweens.
反正我们也没损失
What do we have to lose?
成交吗
So, it's a deal?
麦克斯 疯了
Max, this is fucking insane.
你去受罚
Just take your goddamn punishment.
卢卡斯和我去参趴
Lucas and I will go to the party.
我们会阻止任何人靠近柏丽
We'll cock-block anyone that gets near Brixlee.
他们没有邀请你
They didn't invite you.
什么
What?
万人迷只邀请了我
The popular kids only invited me.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
他们认为你有点不着调
They think you're kind of... random.
但没事的
Oh. - But it's okay,
因为一旦那些人熟悉你
'cause once those guys get to know you,
他们视你会如我 你没有不着调
they'll see what I see, that you're not random.
你好独特
That you're specific.
我不买毒品
I'm not buying drugs.
我也不 -不必你们出马
Neither am I. - You guys don't have to.
我来交涉 你们站着就行
I'll do all the talking. I just need your height in there.
我们之中唯有你 像是大学生
You're the only one of us that looks like they could be in college.
各位
Guys.
干还是不干
Are you in or out?
你们的目的 是为了亲嘴趴
So, you guys did all of this for a kissing party?
不 那里也有很酷的男生
No. There's also gonna be cool boys there.
我记得我第一次亲嘴趴
I remember my first kissing party.
那是马努斯·帕特尔家 六年级后的暑假
It was the summer after sixth grade at Manush Patel's house.
你亲谁了
Who'd you kiss?
马努什的妹妹
Uh, Manush's sister.
等下子 你没同去吗
Wait, you weren't there?
没去 我们那会儿还不熟
No, we didn't really know each other then.
虽同一年级
I mean, we were in the same grade,
但直到八年级 我们才亲密
but we didn't really become close until eighth grade.
我以为你们早就认识了
Oh. I just figured you guys knew each other for longer.
对 最好的朋友都在幼儿园
Yeah, everybody knows you meet your best friends in kindergarten.
你们成了朋友 只是因为住的近
The only reason you're friends with people back then is 'cause you live close to each other.
或因为 你们父母是朋友
Or, because, like, your parents are friends.
不 我们不是这样的
No. That's not true for us.
我们是朋友 是因为我们相互喜欢
We're friends because we like each other.
我们住的也很近 -我们父母是朋友
And we live close together. - And our parents are friends.
好 过来
Okay, come here.
入屋买两片药
Go in. Buy two pills.
找本吉
Ask for Benji.
别提汉娜
Do not mention Hannah.
谁是汉娜 -我是
Who's Hannah? - I am.
我是麦克斯
Oh. I'm Max.
我知道你是谁
Yeah, I know who you are.
好 入屋买药
Okay, just go in there, buy the pills,
然后给你无人机
and then I'll trade you for the drone.
如果情况不妙 开车走人
Okay, if this goes bad, drive off.
好 -好
Okay. - Okay.
现在回头还不晚
It's not too late to turn back.
我们必须买药 换无人机 才能去参趴
No. We have to get the drugs so we can get the drone, so we can go to the party.
有人吗
Hello?
我是你爸
I am your daddy!
你是我宝贝
You are my baby!
你得留在这儿受苦 直到你成为男人
Listen, you will stay down here and suffer until you learn to be men!
听好了 小宝宝该穿什么
Listen! What you babies wearing?
尿布 -那就对了
Diapers! - That's right!
晚上好 我们找本吉
Good evening. We're looking for Benji.
傻缺 过来
Hey, dickless. Come here.
是 爸 -好 你去找本吉
Yes, Daddy. - All right, I need you to go find Benji.
告诉他有访客
Tell him he's got visitors.
是 爸
Yes, Daddy.
我在问你
I ask the fucking questions!
那是你儿子
That's your son?
你们可以坐那边等
You guys can go sit your asses down over there and wait.
不管你怎么样
Whatever happens to you is
是你自己的错
your own fucking fault.
给我20 死小子
Drop and give me 20, you fucking babies!
听
Listen!
四眼仔 起来
Four! Get up!
需要帮忙吗
Can I help you?
下午好
Good afternoon.
我们想买两片莫莉
We would like to buy two pieces of Molly, please.
西玛努兄弟会的拉菲派你们来的吗
Did Rafi from Sigma Nu send you?
是他 那混蛋
He did, that fucker.
你们才七岁
You guys are, like, seven.
除了你 不止七岁
Oh, except for you. I recognize you from econ.
你好 伙计
What's up, man?
说真的 我不卖毒品给儿童
Seriously, I'm not selling drugs to kids.
我们不是儿童 我们是少年
We're not kids. We're tweens.
谁叫你们来的
Who told you to come here?
东西卖我们 你会知道的
Sell us the drugs, and you'll find out.
好
All right.
先坐着
Stay there.
你觉得他要多久
How long do you think he's gonna be?
你让我嗨了
Oh, you made me high.
说谁派你们来的
Tell me who sent you.
汉娜
Hannah.
干嘛 我嗨了
What? I'm high as fuck.
原来她这样利用我
So, this is what she thinks of me, huh?
转告汉娜 如果她想要莫莉
You can tell Hannah that if she wants Molly,
她可以吸我鸡巴
she can suck my dick.
你不该那样说女性
You shouldn't talk about women like that.
除非她同意吸鸡巴
The only time she should suck your dick is when she gives you consent.
你可以吸我鸡巴
You can suck my dick,
你也可以吸我鸡巴
and you can suck my dick, too.
那我呢 我傻坐吗
What about me? I'm just gonna sit here?
我们是精豆小子我们一起上
We're the Bean Bag Boys. We do everything together.
滚出去 小操蛋们
Get the fuck out of here, you little fucking babies.
走
Let's go.
出去
Get out!
兄弟们 等等
Hey, guys, wait.
我有些料 也许令你改变心意
I have something in here that might change your mind.
快点
Hurry up.
誓言 听着
Pledges, listen!
现在谁儿童
Bitch! Now who's the baby?!
我靠 -搞毛啊
Holy shit. - What the fuck?
我拿不到药 我会被禁足
If I don't get those drugs, I'm gonna be grounded,
那我就亲不成柏丽了
and then I'll never get to kiss Brixlee!
麦克斯 你到底在干什么
Max, what the fuck are you doing?
你卖药 我们买药
You sell drugs. We came here to buy them.
所以现在拿药来
So now you're gonna sell us the drugs.
别测试我
Do not test me!
好
Okay.
你要药吗 我又不是你父母 拿去
You want the drugs? I'm not your parent. Here.
谢了
Thanks.
该死
Oh, shit.
你们死定了
Oh, you're fucking dead.
怎么回事
What the fuck's going on down here?
她刚撤销了指控
She just dropped the charges.
天啊
Oh, God.
我靠
Holy shit.
麦克斯 小心
Max, watch out!
我掩护你
I got your back.
索尔
Thor!
你归我了
Your ass is mine!
我天 我刚杀了人
Oh, my God, I just killed a man!
卢卡斯 拿药
Lucas, get the drugs!
我们没来过
We were never here!
快点开车
Start the fucking car!
麦克斯
Max!
怎么了 -快点开车
What's happening? - Fucking go!
什么 -妈的
What? - Shit, shit, shit!
快开车
Drive! Drive!
卢卡斯 药
Lucas, drugs.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
让我看瓶内
Let me see what's in the bottle.
当然可以
Yeah. Of course.
好 给我就行
Okay, just-just give it to me.
你们还超屌的
Wow, you guys are little badasses.
因为我们是精豆小子
'Cause we're the Bean Bag Boys.
什么意思
I don't know what that means.
我们小而弥坚
We have beanbags.
是真货
It's been real, guys.
亲嘴趴开心
Have fun at your kissing party.
谢谢
Thank you.
还1.7英里远
Oh. We're only 1.7 miles away.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我们拿到了无人机 一切解决
We got the drone. Everything worked out.
麦克斯
Max.
我脸上挨了一拳 好吗
I got punched in the fucking face, okay?
我们买了毒
We bought drugs.
现在能回家吗
Can we just go home now?
兄弟们 是我爸
Guys, it's my dad.
爸
Hey, Dad.
我提早上飞机
Hey, buddy. I got on the early flight,
我15分钟后到家
so I'll be home in 15 minutes.
15分钟后 还是延误15分钟
15 minutes from now or 15 minutes from later?
哈哈 好笑
Ha-ha, funny guy.
一会儿见
I'll see you soon.
我爸15分钟后就到家
My dad will be home in 15 minutes.
也许他不会注意到无人机不见了
M-Maybe he won't notice that the drone's gone.
他会注意到的 他很细心
He'll notice. He's very observant.
所以我妈爱上他
That's why my mom fell in love with him.
无人机必须在你爸之前到家
The drone has to be home before your dad.
我知道
I know.
只无人机 不是你
Just the drone. Not you.
只无人机
Just the drone.
好
Okay.
来吧
Here we go.
爽
Yes! - Yes!
小心 -我知道
Careful. - I got this, I got this. Oh!
像风一样飞 麦克斯
Fly like the wind, Max.
此处右转
Yeah, uh, take a right up here.
我能看见你家 -就在那儿
I can see your house. - There it is. There it is.
窗户关着
The windows are closed.
该怎么办 -走烟囱
Shit. What do I do? - The chimney.
非常窄 -你能行
It's very tight. - You got this.
该死 我看不见
Shit! I can't see. I can't see.
摄像头沾了灰
There's ash all over the camera.
使用原力
Use the Force.
不不 我能做到
No, no, I can do this. - Uh...
我熟我家
I know my house perfectly.
我闭眼都行 -好
I can do this with my eyes closed. - Okay.
别搞破坏
Don't break anything.
信我 我行
Trust me, I got this.
耶 -你做到了
Yeah! - You did it! You got it!
耶 -我是最佳飞行员
Yes! - I'm the best pilot ever!
耶
Yes!
我们是成功了 -是
I think we did it. - Yeah.
任务完成
Mission accomplished.
爸
Hey, Dad.
你安全回家了吗
Did you get home safe?
我居然信任你
Cannot believe I trusted you!
我明确告诉你
I explicitly told you,
别碰无人机
do not touch the drone! - Uh-huh.
天哪 -我爱你
Oh, my God. - I love you.
爸
Dad?
爸 请回说"我爱你"
Dad, please... say "I love you" back.
我想听
I need to hear it.
喂
Hello?
我爸说我被禁足了
My dad said that I'm grounded.
我再也不能亲柏丽了
Now I'm never gonna be able to kiss Brixlee.
没事的 麦克斯 会有其他趴的
It's okay, Max. There'll be other parties.
卢卡斯 你不明白 -他是对的 卢卡斯
Lucas, you don't get it. - He's right, Lucas.
这次趴会改变我们的生活
This party could change our lives,
你却不在乎
and you don't even care.
一点也不酷
It's not cool at all.
你会知道什么不酷
Yeah, you would know what's not cool.
几个意思
What the fuck does that mean?
去啜啤酒 奶嘴娃
Go sip a beer, Sippy Cup.
我喜欢啤酒 所以我会去
I love beer, so yes, I will.
你自以为成熟 但事实是
And you may think you're so mature, but the truth is
你没有阴毛 我有六根
you don't have pubes, and I have six.
你说有阴毛还喝啤酒 我知道你没有
You say you have pubes, but you also say you drink beer, and I know you don't.
别吵了
Stop arguing!
承认你不去试演 是因为你觉得很逊
Just admit you skipped the audition because you thought it wasn't cool
虽然你有天赐声线
even though your voice is a fucking gift.
你总大放厥词 却一无是处
And you always talk a big game, and you never back it up.
如同高速公路那次 -抱歉
Like on the freeway. - Oh, sorry.
我不想穿过12条车道 只为你亲小骚货
I didn't want to cross 12 lanes of traffic so you can kiss some skank.
该死 -她不是骚货
Oh, shit. - She's not a skank.
她是我一生挚爱 你收回此话
She's the love of my life. You take that back!
禁止空手道
Hey, no karate.
别打了
Stop fighting!
你不该称女人为"骚货"
You should never call a woman a skank.
你不该乱称呼女人
You should never call a woman anything.
还有你
And you...
你让我们逃学 带着毒品到处跑
You made us ditch school, run around with drugs,
还把警察锁在便利店 用假阳具当门栓
and lock a cop in a convenience store with what I now suspect is a dildo!
你看什么 甘道夫
What the fuck are you looking at, Gandalf?!
你们屁都不懂
You guys don't understand shit.
我体内有荷尔蒙
I have hormones flowing through my body,
逼我疯狂
making me do crazy things.
你们明白用树来摩擦的感受吗
Do you even know what it feels like to want to rub up against a tree all the time?
你以为好过我们
You think you're better than us.
不是好过 是更成熟
Not better, just more mature.
我喜欢浪漫 喜欢当大人
I'm into romance and grown-up shit,
你们还很幼齿
and you guys are still into little kid stuff.
我们如何还能是朋友
I don't even know why we're still friends.
现在取消你的一切最爱
Everything you like is now canceled.
生日被取消 假期被取消
Birthdays are canceled. Holidays are canceled.
取消所有暑假
Summers, canceled.
寒假要来了
Winter is coming.
抱歉 爸 -不不不
I'm sorry, Daddy. - No, no, no.
你不能再喊我为爸
You are no longer allowed to call me Daddy.
叫我安德鲁 或纽曼先生 或典狱长
Call me Andrew or Mr. Newman or Warden.
你那天使小脸底下 魔鬼在其中
Underneath that cherubic face, Devil lives inside you.
我会永远爱你 因为你是我儿子
I will always love you because you are my son,
但我不再喜欢你了
but I no longer like you.
索尔 我刚和麦克斯母亲通电话
Thorny. I just got off the phone with Max's mom.
你知道他逃学还擅自骑车去商场吗
Did you know he skipped school and biked to the mall by himself?
他说的吗 -对
He said that? - He did.
答应我 你永远别犯那种蠢 好吗
Promise me you'll never do something as stupid as that, okay?
我保证
I-I promise.
我们穿越高速公路
And then we ran across the highway,
我手臂脱臼
my arm got ripped out,
有个假女人弹出车外
and a fake woman shot out of a car.
但性药还在我们手里
But we still got the drugs.
但后来 我们用药换了无人机
But then we traded the drone for it,
麦克斯毁了他自己家
and-and Max destroyed his house with it.
所有这一切只因他想娶柏丽
But it was only because he wanted to marry Brixlee,
现在他娶不成了 因为他被永久禁足
and now he can't because he's grounded for life.
我们大吵一顿
And we got into a huge fight,
精豆小子解散
and the Bean Bag Boys are broke up, and...
我有没有麻烦 -好 儿子
Am I in trouble? - Okay, son.
现在听着 我也喜欢嘴炮说故事 好吗
Now, look, I love a good story with a bunch of gibberish just as much as anybody, okay?
我知你正经历压力期
And I know you're going through a stressful time.
但这不足以你对我们扯谎
But it doesn't give you a reason to tell us fibs.
我没扯谎
I'm not fibbing.
我百分百肯定你扯谎
I'm 100% sure you're fibbing to me.
我没扯谎 -好 我都明白了
I'm not fibbing. - Okay. I think I understand what's happening here.
你以为你失去了我们
You think you're losing us,
现在你担心还会失去朋友
and now you're worried you're gonna lose your friends, too.
看我
Look at me, man.
我们会永远在 对吗 我是说 看看
We'll always be there, right? I mean, and look,
别误会我
don't get me wrong.
我和你妈 不同于初初相见那会儿了
You know, me and your mom are not the same people we were when we first met.
有时想分开
Tend to grow apart sometimes.
但没事的
But-but it's okay.
还记得你的寄居蟹吗
You remember your hermit crab?
赫尔曼? 记得 -对 赫尔曼
Herman? Yeah. - That's right. Herman.
还记得它为什么死吗 -那个混...
And you remember why he died? - Oh, son of a...
你说蟹逃了的
You told me he ran away!
没错 它是逃了 但后来死了
Technically, yes, he ran away, but then he died.
天哪 怎么死的
Oh, my gosh. How?
赫尔曼之死 是因为寄居蟹长大了
Herman died because hermit crabs grow out of their shells,
它们得找新壳
and they need to find new,
海滩上 有更大的贝壳可供居住
bigger seashells on the beach to grow into,
不然会死 基本如此
or they die, and we didn't know that.
赫尔曼是因你们而死的?
So, Herman died because of you guys?
重点是
The point is...
你和你朋友在成长变化
you and your friends are growing and changing,
你们都要找更大的壳
and y'all need to find bigger shells.
这并没错
And there's nothing wrong with that.
你得怪宠物店主
Okay, look, you need to blame those pet store owners,
因为他们没教怎么养好寄居蟹
okay, because they did not give us the information about hermit crabs...
我是卢卡斯
It's Lucas.
你吓屎我了
You scared the shit out of me.
我不想你父母看到我脸
I didn't want your parents to see my face.
你为什么来
Why are you even here?
刚才两小时 我成熟了很多
I've grown a lot in the last two hours.
我父母离婚 确实的改变了我
My parents' divorce has really changed me.
如果精豆小子不一起成长
If the Bean Bag Boys don't grow together,
就得分开
they'll grow apart.
我不想那样
I don't want that.
我不想和你离婚
I don't want to get a divorce from you.
那你得去索伦的趴
Then you need to go to Soren's party.
你偷溜出去 -我不能 我被禁足
You need to sneak out. - I can't. I'm grounded.
此外 柏丽的项链还在窑里
Besides, Brixlee's necklace is still in the kiln.
项链交给我
Let me worry about the necklace.
你父母能怎样 双重禁足你么
And what are your parents gonna do, double-ground you?
柏丽到底是不是你的永远
Is Brixlee your forever or not?
那你现在跟我走
Then you need to come with me now.
好 我去 但我不向索尔道歉
Fine, I'll go, but I'm not apologizing to Thor.
他不来了 -很好
He's not coming. - Good.
操那个婊子
Fuck that bitch.
我去拿外套
I'll go get my jacket.
麦克斯 -怎么
Hey, Max. - Yeah?
带上鸡巴
Bring that dick.
你说索尔不来的
You said Thor wasn't coming.
他来是闹哪样
What the hell is he doing here?
你们俩 由我监管
I Parent-Trapped your asses.
瞧 现在我们共享一具更大的寄居蟹壳
See, now we're all in a bigger hermit crab shell together.
我终于理解父母的话了
It made sense when my parents said it.
所以你是怪我们
So, you took the blame for us, huh?
对 我预测了你 然后反其道行之
Yeah. I thought about what you would do, and did the opposite.
这趴 将是史诗狂欢
This party, it's gonna be an epic rager.
好的 奶嘴娃
Okay, Sippy Cup.
别阻挡我 麦生棉条
Just stay out of my way, Maxi Pad.
(Maxi Pad 一种卫生棉条)
可爱仔喔
Aw, don't you boys look cute.
大家都在地下室
Everybody's in the basement.
我都不想知下面什么场面
I don't even want to know what's going on down there.
进来吧 小伙子们
Come on in, fellas.
嗨
Hi.
嗨 您好
Hi there. Oh.
天 你可来了
Oh, my God, you made it.
麦克斯 她是柏丽
Max, I want you to meet Brixlee.
嗨 我是麦克斯
Hi. I'm Max.
嗨
Hi.
很高兴终于见到你
It's nice to finally meet you.
我也是
You, too.
很酷的外套
Cool jacket.
谢谢
Thank you.
我一个人选的 和我妈
I got it all by myself, with my mom.
我也和妈妈一起购物
I go shopping with my mom, too.
春风得意啊
This is going so well.
你带了项链吗
Did you bring the necklace?
柏丽 这是给你的
Brixlee, this is for you.
谢谢 很漂亮
Oh, thanks. It's pretty.
这些是铝珠
They're an-al.
奇妙
Ooh, fancy.
我以后再戴
I'm gonna wear this later.
谢了 麦克斯
Thanks, Max.
如何呀 奶嘴娃
What's up, Sippy Cup?
还行
Not much.
和一堆人干架 还偷了啤酒
Just, uh, got into a fight with a bunch of men and, uh, stole a beer.
奶嘴娃不会喝的
There's no way Sippy Cup is gonna drink it.
我不仅要喝
Not only am I gonna drink it,
还要打破纪录
I'm gonna break the record.
我要喝四口
I'm gonna take four sips.
四口 不可能
Four is impossible.
索伦都破不了四 -闭嘴
Soren can't even do four. - Shut up.
喝
Drink.
一
That's one.
小事儿
Big deal.
二
That's two.
继续
Mm-kay.
三
That's three!
疯了吧
This is insane.
他会吐的
He's gonna barf.
来人 拿奶嘴给他
Somebody get him a sippy cup.
奶嘴娃 奶嘴娃
Sippy Cup! Sippy Cup!
奶嘴娃 奶嘴娃 奶嘴娃
Sippy Cup! Sippy Cup! Sippy Cup!
奶嘴娃 奶嘴
Sippy Cup! Sippy...
四了
That's fucking four!
妈呀
Oh, fuck!
索尔 索尔 索尔 索尔
Thor! Thor! Thor! Thor!
索尔 索尔 索尔
Thor! Thor! Thor! Thor! Thor!
我是死酒鬼
I'm a fucking alcoholic!
不会吧
No way!
四口 猛啊
Four sips. Badass.
敬索尔
Mad respect to Thor.
看过来
Eyes up here.
不同意亲嘴 没问题
If you don't consent to kissing, that's cool.
你可以上楼打电玩
You can go play VR upstairs.
但如果你留下
But if you're staying down here,
你最好稳住
you better strap in,
因为都玩真的
because shit's about to get real.
好啊
Hell yeah. Okay.
转瓶子先
Let's spin a bottle.
我正好有瓶子
Well, then it's a good thing I got a bottle right here!
我退出
I'm out.
等等 你要去哪 -恶心啊
Wait, where are you going? - That was nasty.
我去楼上打电玩
I'm going upstairs to play VR.
如果离开 不可再回来
If you leave, you can never come back.
好得很
Oh, no.
柏丽
Brixlee...
该你了
your turn.
来吧 拜托
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
天哪 超级戏剧了
Oh, my God. This is the most dramatic thing I've ever seen.
他不会的
He's not gonna do it.
他会的
He's gonna do it.
我做不到
I can't do it.
人性难改 他还是奶嘴娃
People don't change. He's still Sippy Cup.
等等
Wait, wait.
是亲嘴娃
Kissy Cup.
亲嘴娃
Kissy Cup!
亲嘴娃 亲嘴娃
Kissy Cup! Kissy Cup!
亲嘴娃 亲嘴
Kissy Cup! Kissy...
滚了 阿提库斯 他叫索尔
Fuck off, Atticus! His name is Thor.
大家都知道你妈抄袭了她的菜谱
And everyone knows your mom plagiarized her cookbook.
索尔 等一下
Thor, wait up.
抱歉 之前叫你苦逼劳力
I'm sorry I called you a try-hard.
不 你是对的
Nah, you were right.
一直以来 我不是我
This whole time, I've been trying to be someone who I wasn't.
我戴耳环
I got an earring.
我喝啤酒
I drank a beer.
我不再唱歌
I quit singing.
我今天也有点疯
I guess I went a little crazy today, too.
我们走
Let's get out of here.
不 你别走
No. You don't want to do that.
你要留下亲柏丽
You're gonna stay down here and kiss Brixlee.
精豆小子一起上
The Bean Bag Boys do everything together.
不是一切
Not everything.
不再是了
Not anymore.
也许那两大姐没错
Maybe those old girls were right.
也许我们道不同
Maybe we're on different paths.
嗯
Yeah.
你打算怎么办
Then what are you gonna do?
我不知道 但不是今次
I don't know. I just know it's not this.
不会吧
No way.
疯了
This is insane.
忘了转瓶子
Forget spin the bottle.
现在去亲你未来的老婆
Now, go over there and kiss your future wife.
拜
Bye.
柏丽 我能亲你吗
Brixlee, can I kiss you?
好
Okay.
安啦
Cool.
我在哪
Where am I?
我在这
Oh, here I am.
卢卡斯 我要走了
Lucas, I'm leaving.
你不试试吗
You sure you don't want to try this?
我算了
Nah, I'm good.
去我家玩"创世纪-飞升"吗
Want to go to my house and play Ascension?
我不再玩了
I don't want to play Ascension anymore.
那我和谁一起玩
Then who am I gonna play with?
你会找到人的
You'll find someone.
我脸痛
My face feels so tingly.
不会吧
No way.
天哪 太神奇了
Oh, my God. This is amazing!
真不敢相信你们在这
I can't believe you guys are here.
太神奇了
Oh, this is so amazing.
嗨 -嗨 -坐下
Hi. - Oh, hi. - Sit down.
请别 别杀我们
Please no, please no. Don't kill us.
看这小脸
Look what happened.
你怎么认识索伦的
How do you know Soren?
他是你男友吗
Is he your boyfriend?
他是我弟 我爱那小混蛋
He's my brother. I love that piece of shit.
其他人呢
You guys, where's everybody else?
你们那个悲伤眼神小友呢
Where's your friend with the sad eyes?
悲伤男孩麦克斯 -在地下室亲嘴
Sad boy Max. - In the basement kissing.
在恣意放纵
It's an orgy down there.
你们不喜欢吗
And you guys aren't into that?
不 -没关系的
Mm-mm. - Aw, it's okay.
你才上六年级
You're only in sixth grade.
以后会明白的
You guys are gonna figure it out.
你有一辈子的时间 别着急
Yeah, you have your whole life for that. No rush. - Yeah.
别着急 - 别着急
No rush. - No rush.
我说 你爱什么
I mean, what do you love?
创世纪 规则 禁毒运动
Ascension, rules, antidrug campaigns...
烤奶酪
grilled cheese.
我现在超想吃烤奶酪
Mmm. - Oh, I could fuck with a grilled cheese right now.
我要去烤奶酪
Aw... - Guys, I'm gonna make us grilled cheese.
听起来不错 -不错
Oh, yeah. That sounds so good. - Nice.
你呢 无袖仔 你迷什么
What about you, sleeveless? What are you into?
我迷唱歌
I love to sing.
好
Yes.
其实我今天没参加音乐剧试演
I actually skipped my audition today for the musical.
不 -我现在没机会了
No. - Now I can't be in it.
不 -什么 你必须说服他们让你试演
No. - What? You have to convince them to let you audition.
你必须 你必须
You must. You must.
试演 -嘘 为我们唱
Audition. - Shh. Sing for us.
不 -天哪
No. - Oh, my God.
为我们唱 你是小小鸟
Sing for us. You're a baby bird.
不 来吧 我们错过了音乐会
No, come on. We missed our concert.
为我们唱 -没烤奶酪吃了么
Sing for us. - So, no grilled cheese?
为我们唱 -不
Sing for us. Sing for us. - No.
为我们开音乐会
Be our concert.
我得花点时间
♪ I-I gotta take a little time ♪
花点时间思考
♪ A little time to think things over ♪
读出言下之意
♪ I better read between the lines ♪
以防日后需要
♪ In case I need it when I'm older ♪
这山我必须爬
♪ Now this mountain I must climb ♪
感觉肩挑世界
♪ Feels like the world upon my shoulders ♪
但是透过云彩 我看到爱闪耀
♪ But through the clouds I see love shine ♪
当生活暗淡时 它能让我温暖
♪ It keeps me warm as life grows colder ♪
在我生命之中
♪ In my life ♪
有心痛有疼痛
♪ There's been heartache and pain ♪
我却不再知道
♪ I don't know ♪
能否再次面对
♪ If I can face it again ♪
我现在不能停
♪ I can't stop now ♪
我行了这么远
♪ I've traveled so far ♪
为改孤独人生
♪ To change this lonely life ♪
我想了解真爱
♪ I want to know what love is ♪
我要你给我看
♪ I want you to show me ♪
我想感受真爱
♪ I want to feel what love is ♪
我知你会秀爱
♪ I know you can show me ♪
我得花点时间
♪ I gotta take a little time ♪
花点时间环顾
♪ A little time to look around me ♪
我无处可躲藏
♪ And I got nowhere left to hide ♪
看起来是爱情
♪ It looks like love has ♪
终于找到了我
♪ Finally found me ♪
在我生命之中
♪ In my life ♪
有心痛有疼痛
♪ There's been heartache and pain ♪
我却不再知道 能否再次面对
♪ I don't know if I can face it again ♪
我现在不能停
♪ I can't stop now ♪
我行过这么远
♪ I've traveled so far ♪
为改孤独人生
♪ To change this lonely life ♪
我想知道真爱
♪ I want to know what love is ♪
我知你可秀爱
♪ I know you can show me ♪
我想知道真爱
♪ I want to know what love is ♪
我知你可秀爱
♪ I know you can show me, oh ♪
我们来谈谈爱
♪ Let's talk about love ♪
我想知道真爱
♪ I want to know what love is ♪
爱上心之所爱
♪ Love that you feel inside ♪
我知你可秀爱
♪ I know you can show me ♪
我超想知道啊
♪ I want to know. ♪
我的杰作
My masterpiece.
谢谢 我真棒
Thank you. I was really great.
你好 麦克斯
What's up, Max?
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
没想到你会来 -你开玩笑吗
Hey. I didn't think you'd make it. - Are you kidding?
我永远不会错过你的演出
You know I'd never miss one of your shows.
你刺了皮条客 太酷了
It was so cool when you stabbed that pimp.
谢谢
Thank you.
抱歉 索尔 这是丝康特
Oh, sorry. Thor, this is Scout.
你真行 -谢了 亲爱的
You were really good. - Thanks, sweetie.
我日场 演得更好
I was much better in the matinee.
我去找卡西迪
I'm gonna go find Cassidy.
我以为你还在禁足期
I thought you were still grounded.
昨天结束了 简直像洞中一月
It ended yesterday. A month in the hole.
再次感谢你背锅
Thanks again for taking the fall.
换你也这样的
You would've done the same.
好好好
Well, well, well.
看看谁来了 是我
Look who's here. Me.
嘿
Hey!
感觉好几星期没说话似的
Feels like we haven't talked in weeks.
嗯
Yeah.
麦克斯
Max.
我妈说 如果你妈来接 就送我们去吃冷冻酸奶
My mom said she'll drop us at frozen yogurt if your mom will pick us up.
好的 稍等 宝贝
Great. Be there in a second, babe.
好 宝贝
Okay, babe.
与丝康特如何
So, how's it going with Scout?
好
Good.
辛苦但值得
But hard. But good.
打理关系 事儿多
A relationship is a lot of work.
别让别人指点你
Don't let anyone tell you differently.
卢卡斯 还和我们玩创世纪吗
Hey. Uh, Lucas, you still want to play Ascension with me and the guys later?
我一会儿就去 -永远的卢卡斯
I'll be there in a minute. - Classic Lucas.
卡洛斯和反霸凌联盟 看起来很酷
Carlos and those SCAB guys seem cool.
是很酷
They're cool.
但他们毕竟不是精豆小子
But they're not the Bean Bag Boys.
麦克斯
Max.
好
All right.
我该走了
I guess, I guess I should go.
好
Yeah, all right.
Well...
嗯
Yeah.
我想你们
I missed you guys.
我们许诺吧
Let's make a promise.
即便不能腻在一起
Even if we don't hang out all the time,
我们还是会成大事
we'll still always be there for the big stuff.
永远的精豆小子
Bean Bag Boys for life.
等等
Wait.
我有东西给你们看
There's something I have to show you.
三分钟后 去我父母卧室
Come up to my parents' bedroom in three minutes.
兄弟们 看
Yo, guys, check this out.
室内秋千?
An indoor swing?
你总有最棒的玩具
You always have the best toys.
耶
Yeah!
开灯
Flip that switch.
有多酷
How cool is it?
你父母城会玩
Your parents love to play.
做什么用的 -用来晃啊
What do they do with it? - They swing on it.
我们能玩吗 -成
Can we go on it? - Fuck yeah.
索尔
Thor?
你们在爸妈房间里干嘛
What are you doing in Mom and Dad's room?
滚出去 安娜贝尔
Get the hell out of here, Annabelle!
那秋千是性用品 干炮用的
That swing is for sexing. People do sex on it.
翻译： 微博@电灯泡diandp
原创不易，无论如何，请保留译者姓名，谢谢